

CONTACT

0430 617 770
ellijayne.m.willard@gmail.com
Portfolio: https://ellijayne.github.io
Github: https://github.com/ellijayne
Sydney, Australia

EDUCATION

General Assembly

Web Development: 2018

Western Sydney University

B.A. Social Sciences (Criminology & Laws)

SKILLS

HTML & CSS

Sass

JavaScript

jQuery & Underscore

Ruby on Rails

PostgreSQL

Responsive Web Design

Agile Methodologies

REFERENCES

References available on request

EJ WILLARD

WEB DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

I am a creative Web Developer with a background in the legal profession. My professional experience has taught me discipline and how important continuous learning is, which I feel really jives well with the tech world. The most exciting part about this change is being able to use my creativity, there is no better feeling than seeing your work come to life in the browser.

I also love the diversity of talent that the tech world attracts and am looking forward to working with an innovative company that has a fantastic culture!

EXPERIENCE

General Assembly

June 2018 to August 2018 \parallel Web Development Immersive Student

Worked on many major works including:

- > Kana-o-Manabu (built with HTML, SassCSS, JavaScript/jQuery, WanaKana.js, Ruby on Rails and PostgreSQL).
- > Music/Vinyl Database (built with HTML, sassCSS, Ruby on Rails and PostgreSQL. Deployed on Heroku: https://audiophiles.herokuapp.com/).
- > Dating App (developed as part of a team. Built with HTML, sassCSS, Ruby on Rails, PostgreSQL, JavaScript, AJAX and various APIs. Deployed on Heroku: https://todo-meetyou.herokuapp.com/).

Hunt & Hunt Lawyers

May 2016 - June 2018 || Paralegal

Worked on the Defendant side of Personal Injury Claims. Provided primary support for Senior Counsel & Partners. Managing competing interests of clients and constantly negotiating with different stakeholders to obtain the right outcome for them. The role involved keeping on top of the constant legislative changes and new case law that impacted upon the cases we were running.

Slater & Gordon Lawyers

 $March\ 2015$ - $May\ 2016\ ||\ Senior\ Legal\ Assistant$ Worked in a client facing position on the Plaintiff side of Personal Injury Claims involving former NSW Police Officers.

JB HIFI

November 2013 - March 2015 || Software Department Coordinator Worked in a client facing position, managing a team of Media Advisors.